const questions = {
  questions:[
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'nii',
      font: 'kulitan',
      options: ['Mo', 'Ní-Nî', 'Mi', 'Da'],
      correctAnswer: 'Ní-Nî',
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'no',
      options: ['Be', 'Bang', 'No', 'Gu' ],
      correctAnswer: 'No',
    },
{
  id: 3,
  question: 'nu',
  options: ['Po', 'Nu', 'Kú-Kû', 'Su' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Nu',
},
{
  id: 4,
  question: 'nuu',
  options: ['Nú-Nû', 'Lang', 'Yu', 'Ge' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Nú-Nû',
},
{
  id: 5,
  question: 'Pang',
  options: ['Sang', 'Mang', 'Pang', 'Lang' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Pang',
},
{
  id: 6,
  question: 'paa',
  options: ['Pá-pâ', 'Be', 'Ki', 'La' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Pá-pâ',
},
{
  id: 7,
  question: 'pe',
  options: ['Po', 'Pe', 'Pi', 'Pu' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Pe',
},
  {
    id: 8,
    question: 'pi',
    options: ['Pi', 'Ko', 'Lo', 'Sa' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Pi',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: 'pii',
    options: ['Pi', 'Pí-pî', 'Dang', 'Pa' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Pí-pî',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: 'po',
    options: ['Yu', 'Kang', 'Lú-Lû', 'Po' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Po',
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: 'pu',
    options: ['Pu', 'Má-Mâ', 'Pa', 'Ga' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Pu',
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: 'puu',
    options: ['Mang', 'Sang', 'Pang', 'Pú-pû' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Pú-pû',
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: 'sang',
    options: ['Gu', 'Ngi', 'Pi', 'Sang' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Sang',
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: 'saa',
    options: ['Mo', 'Sá-Sâ', 'Ki', 'Si' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Sá-Sâ',
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: 'se',
    options: ['Du', 'Se', 'Gu', 'Mí-Mî' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Se',
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: 'Si',
    options: ['Yo', 'Gi', 'Si', 'Mo' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Si',
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: 'sii',
    options: ['Mu', 'Dú-Dû', 'Gu', 'Sí-Sî' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Sí-Sî',
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: 'so',
    options: ['So', 'Mú-Mû', 'Bang', 'Ko' ],
    correctAnswer: 'So',
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: 'su',
    options: ['Ki', 'Mú-Mû', 'Ná-Nâ', 'Su' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Su',
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: 'suu',
    options: ['Go', 'Sú-Sû', 'Nang', 'Se' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Sú-Sû',
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: 'tang',
    options: ['Ngang', 'Tang', 'Nang', 'Mang' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Tang',
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: 'taa',
    options: ['Tá-Tâ', 'Nga', 'Tang', 'Lu' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Tá-Tâ',
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: 'te',
    options: ['Ne', 'Te', 'Ke', 'Be' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Te',
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: 'Ti',
    options: ['Nge', 'Gí-Gî', 'Bi', 'Ti' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Ti',
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: 'tii',
    options: ['Pi', 'Tí-Tî', 'Ni', 'Yi' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Tí-Tî',
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question: 'to',
    options: ['To', 'Bo', 'Sang', 'Pe' ],
    correctAnswer: 'To',
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question: 'tu',
    options: ['Pu', 'Ngo', 'Tu', 'Ko' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Tu',
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question: 'tuu',
    options: ['Tú-Tû', 'Pu', 'Da', 'Ngu' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Tú-Tû',
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question: 'wa',
    options: ['Bang', 'Kí-Kî', 'Ngú-Ngû', 'Wa' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Wa',
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    question: 'wang',
    options: ['Nga', 'Ge', 'Pi', 'Wang' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Wang',
  },

  ]
  };
  
  export default questions;